You're the only one here so far, Yagami?
Hey, Utomiya-kun.
I had a feeling you'd be
the Class C representative.
Though I'm not convinced
I'm cut out for leadership.
I'm sure the others realized
how responsible you were.
We've lost one of our own.
I take that loss extremely seriously.
I didn't expect Hatano-kun
to get expelled, either.
It's a terrible shame.
Yes.
Do you think Hosen will come?
I'd give it 50-50 odds.
I'd bet on no.
Class D won't work with anyone
unless they get points out of it.
I think that's why he might come.
If he doesn't, we'll form our own
group without Class D for sure.
Far from being in demand then,
they'll be left out in the cold.
Hey, Riku, Takuya!
I knew it'd be you two.
They're still making you do
all the dirty work, Osamu-kun?
Our leader hates the dirty work.
That makes me the fall guy.
We just waiting on Kazuomi?
Wouldn't it be better for
us to work without him?
The deserted island test will require
skills other than pure academics.
Class D may be the
lowest-ranked class overall,
but they're first in Physical
Ability by a narrow margin.
I think they could play a crucial
role in group formation.
I get what you're saying, Riku.
Our Class A is annoyed about Kazuomi's
attitude of demanding points
in exchange for cooperation, too.
But I don't think we should
count them out just yet.
I acknowledge that Class D
has a great deal to offer,
but I don't think it's worth
trying to curry favor with Hosen.
Looks like you won't get your wish, Riku.
Classroom of the Elite 4th Season 2nd Year 1st Term
So you're ready to pay up, are you?
Is that supposed to be funny?
We're not paying you a single point.
#7 Plotting
Let's all settle down, now.
We can't negotiate if we start
out at each other's throats.
Now that we're all here,
let's get started, then.
I didn't say I was ready to start!
Hosen, I'm going to ask you
to refrain from violence here.
Oh? You gonna stop me, then?
I will if I have to.
Sounds fun.
Show me what you can do, then!
This is ridiculous.
But if that's what you want,
I'll respond in kind...
on the condition that you leave
my classmates alone forever.
Hey, now, what's that supposed to mean?
I know who got Hatano expelled.
And you think it was me?
Who else could it be?
Calm down, you two!
Right now, we need to focus on the
deserted island survival game.
Did I say I was here to talk about that?
Then did you just come here to kill time?
What if I did?
I refuse to believe you're that stupid.
Both the second- and third-years
have been through this test before.
We need to recognize that we're
at a severe disadvantage.
If we can't work together,
they'll eat us all alive.
That's coward talk, Yagami.
I'm not afraid of the upperclassmen.
I can crush 'em all.
Not everyone is as blessed as you are.
The fact of the matter
is that first-years,
as a whole, are at a disadvantage.
I think it's necessary for
first-years to work together
and make at least one
powerful group of four.
A group of students who
can easily compete with the
upperclassmen, like you said.
You're proposing that we don't
compete with each other for class points
this time?
Yes. Unlike the upperclassman, who don't
have much time before graduation,
we'll have more than enough
time for that moving forward.
So we should abandon this
as a race for class points.
I'm not sure that's sufficient reason
for us to team up with each other.
We'll have far more to lose if
the upperclassmen trample us.
Wait a minute, Takuya.
Why just one group?
If the idea is to have groups
meet up for the main event,
wouldn't it be better to
have multiple strong groups?
You're right, of course.
But if we do that from the start,
we risk dividing our power.
It's important to make the
strongest possible group of four
that can definitely take first place.
Since the upperclassmen
can only have a maximum of three people
from three classes working together.
And if we can take first place, we don't
have to worry about the rest at all?
Even if Hosen-kun refuses and
it's just our three classes,
we'll just use the same strategy
as the other grade years.
We first-years are given the privilege
of forming small groups
of up to four people.
It would be a waste to
just throw that away.
So I want you to help me.
Sure, I'm willing to help out.
What are you up to, Hosen?
Why should I be up to something?
You made your cute little request for my
help, and I'm willing to entertain it.
What are your conditions?
For the large group when we get there,
I want the two empty slots
to be Class D students.
That's my must-have.
What?
But we still don't know if we'll get
to choose our large groups or not.
I told you, that's my must-have.
I see. So if we can't let
in two Class D students,
we'll have to complete the
test with just the four.
Don't mess around, Hosen.
I'm not messing around.
If you don't like it, you can drop out.
You son of a...
Calm down, Utomiya-kun.
I think his conditions are acceptable.
Our priority should be unity
between the four of us.
If we give him an inch now,
he'll take a mile later.
And if we let Class D go now,
you think that will change his attitude?
Well...
The most important thing now is
that the first-years win this test.
We should set aside everything else.
I agree with him, Riku.
I understand how you feel,
but first-year unity has to come first.
So as long as you get that,
you're fine with anything else, Hosen?
Do what you want.
So, are we heading to Yukimoo's room?
I'm fine with it, but we're
going to study, not hang out.
Yeah, I know.
Ayanokoji-kun!
Are you free for a minute?
What is it?
There's a first-year who
wants to speak to you.
Do you think you'd be able to see them?
What's this, Kiyo-pon?
Think some little kohai
has a crush on you?
I-Is that what it is?!
If it is, I'm afraid
I can't give my blessing.
Is that what it is?
Well, it's actually a boy
who wants to talk to you...
Sorry.
Seems fine to me.
It's good to make more inroads
with the first-years.
Yeah. Since our group isn't
exactly outgoing, either.
Y-Yes. It's fine with me if you go, then.
All right.
Looks like he's coming.
Let's wait here.
It seems like you've gotten close
with the first-years already.
Huh? Well, it's already July.
We've had plenty of time.
I'm sure you've made a few friends
among the first-years yourself!
I wouldn't go that far just yet.
R-Really?
Well, no need to rush, I suppose.
There's lots of time left!
Kushida-senpai!
This is the one who wanted to
meet you. His name is Yagami-kun.
It's a pleasure to meet
you, Ayanokoji-senpai.
Thank you for making
time to speak with me.
You're in Class 1-B, right?
Yes!
I'm Yagami Takuya!
I actually have to tell you something.
Are you aware of the extremely limited
special test that's been offered
to the first-years?
Um, I'm afraid I haven't
heard anything about this...
Do you mind if I talk in front of her?
I have no right to stop you.
Soon after we came to the school,
we got a communique from President Nagumo.
Whoever gets you expelled before
the second term begins will
be paid 20 million points.
What? You have to expel Ayanokoji-kun?
And 20 million... That's so much!
Is that really allowed?
I understand now that this was an
extremely unusual special test.
I also have no interest in getting
rewarded for sabotaging someone else,
so I have no intention of participating.
But why Ayanokoji-kun?
The president said he was chosen
at random from the second-years.
But didn't it seem strange
to have a special test that
wasn't officially issued by the school?
Acting Chairman Tsukishiro was present
when the president told us about it.
It seemed like a legitimate setting
in which to be issued a special test.
The acting chairman was there?
Yeah, I guess that does seem legitimate...
In attendance from Class 1-A were
Takahashi Osamu-kun and Ishigami Kyo-kun.
From Class B, it was me.
From Class C, it was Utomiya Riku-kun.
And from Class D, it was Hosen
Kazuomi-kun and Nanase Tsubasa-san.
What made you decide to tell me about it?
I heard that Hosen-kun took
his chance at it, but failed.
And he did it in the most
barbaric way possible.
I won't deny that.
One other thing.
I determined that if I don't act,
it's possible that your classmate,
Kushida-senpai, could
end up harmed, as well.
I appreciate the concern, but it could
be dangerous for you to tell me this.
Will you be all right, Yagami-kun?
If this gets out...
It's okay, Kushida-senpai.
He didn't mention anything
about penalties.
And I'm prepared to be hated by a
certain segment of the first-years.
We'll have to fight the other
classes sooner or later anyway.
Please be careful, Ayanokoji-senpai.
All right.
So, is there anyone you're
particularly worried about?
Let me see.
Hosen-kun seems like the
most likely subject,
but if I had to name one in particular...
No, I won't say it.
Why not? Now I'm curious!
If I give their name now,
you'll put a target on their back.
As a fellow first-year,
I don't think that would be fair.
And I'm not completely certain
of their character yet.
During the upcoming special
test, I want to see for myself
if they're dangerous or not.
You be careful now, Yagami-kun.
I will.
And... I'm okay to wait until
after the test is over,
but I want to talk to you, Kushida-senpai.
Oh, okay.
I wonder what it could be about!
That's a fine kohai you've got.
Yeah. I'm really not worthy of him...
Not that I'm happy about it.
Yagami-kun knows about my past.
And?
I'll need to get rid of him soon.
Getting rid of a lowerclassman
will be harder than getting
rid of me or Horikita.
That depends on how I go about it.
The smarter someone thinks they are,
the more easily they're disposed of.
You and Horikita-san aren't exceptions.
I thought we had a truce.
Sure, I'll be a good girl for now!
See you later, Ayanokoji-kun!
Hey. Can we talk?
I'm sorry to approach you
under these conditions.
What do you want to talk about?
It's about Hosen Kazuomi.
You've experienced his uncooperative
attitude by now, I'm sure.
We want to deal him a blow
during the survival game.
He doesn't have a lot of
private points at the moment.
If we force him to drop out early,
he won't be able to pay the penalty.
So you want to get Hosen expelled?
Hell yes!
I mean, yes, that's correct.
Mind if I ask why?
Another member of Class 1-C,
Hatano, was expelled.
I'm positive that Hosen was involved.
And you want revenge?
I would be lying if I said
I didn't hold a grudge.
But the most important thing is
to prevent any future expulsions.
Yeah. We lost a hundred
class points from that.
So, what does that have to do with me?
Hosen has refused to work with
anyone outside his class.
But you partnered with him
during the April test.
So you think I have special access to him?
Please help me.
It's hard to agree when we don't
yet know what the test entails.
Then will you agree to consider the offer?
If we can eliminate Hosen
early and get him expelled,
I'll pay you a considerable reward.
You haven't considered that
I might be Hosen's ally?
Well...
That wound on your hand.
You got it in a fight with
Hosen-kun, didn't you?
What makes you think that?
Because we were after the
20-million-point bounty, too.
I see.
Is that why you approached
me that evening,
pretending to search for a partner?
That's right.
But I doubt you had a way
of getting just me expelled if
I had agreed to work with you.
Don't know what to tell you there.
I apologize about that.
But we've withdrawn from that test.
Why?
Even if we did succeed
at having you expelled,
that would quickly become
known throughout the school.
We'd make an enemy of
the entire Class 2-D.
Wouldn't getting Hosen expelled
result in the same?
That seems doubtful.
I suspect more of his classmates
will be glad to be rid of him.
Just keep it in mind, would you?
All we want is to see Hosen expelled.
Tick tock.
I really hate that noisy watch of yours.
Oh, shut up.
You don't know how much this
watch is worth, do you?
I don't waste my time researching
the prices of things I hate.
So, what did you want?
It's about the deserted island test.
Partner up with me, Amasawa.
You want my help, huh?
And on a deserted island...
You got sexy things in mind?
Wanna see my panties?
I'll give you a glimpse if you'd like.
You think I won't hit a woman?
Relax. I'm sure you'd
hit absolutely anyone.
Then you better cut
the bullshit real fast.
Let me ask you this, then.
Why include me in your plan?
You've got the guts to dive headfirst
into getting Ayanokoji expelled.
For a 20-million-point jackpot?
Who wouldn't?
So, what are you offering?
We're supposed to be equals here.
We discussed that earlier, didn't we?
I see. A group thought up by
Hosen-kun, including Nanase-chan...
But who's our fourth?
Don't need one.
The winner of the deserted island
test will be the three of us.
You seem very confident about that.
But what about the plan to have
the four classes work together
to make the strongest possible group?
I figured one of you two would
be the Class D representative.
That's up to me, the leader
of Class D, to decide.
You see what I'm getting at?
You're going to send in a lesser
being as your representative?
You're picking a fight from all sides.
As long as we send in someone
sufficiently smart or strong,
it won't seem suspicious.
And Hosen-kun joining the four-class
group would cause problems of its own.
Yeah, he doesn't seem
like the teamwork type.
So, let's get down to brass tacks.
How much will you pay me?
We won't be paying you.
I will stress again that we are equals.
But our contributions won't
be equal, now, will they?
I'm positive I can contribute in any
setting, deserted island included.
It'll likely require stamina.
Can our sweet little doll
Nanase-chan hope to keep up?
Would you like to try me?
Well, you're quite bold.
Hey, maybe you've got
what it takes after all.
I just love strong women.
You seem rather exceptional yourself.
Oh, do I?
Me, Nanase, and you will
form a three-person group.
Got that?
I'll admit that Nanase-chan
has the physicality.
But I'd still like a bonus
for helping you out.
You think pretty highly of yourself, huh?
Tell me, then. What do you
want besides the group reward?
I want all the points for
expelling Ayanokoji-senpai.
That's my condition.
Man, you're pretty damn full of yourself.
Can't agree to that.
I guess it'll be a no from me, then.
But are you sure you can
afford to lose my interest?
You're picking fights on all sides.
Might be hard with no one you
can trust besides Nanase-chan.
Of course, if we expel Ayanokoji-senpai,
all the glory will go to you.
That's enough, isn't it?
You don't need to accept her terms.
If we give the whole 20 million
to Class A, moving forward—
Oh, shut up.
Amasawa, you can have the reward.
Aw, thanks!
I've always thought a man's most
appealing trait is his generosity.
Well, see you at the test.
Are you sure about this?
She seems like a backstabber to me.
I haven't trusted you
or her from the start.
Why work with her, then?
She's not like the other
trash around here.
Like you, she's got hidden depths.
That may be true.
But 20 million feels like
a steep price to pay.
Who gives a damn about
some verbal agreement?
If I get that guy expelled,
the reward gets paid out to me.
She can cry all she wants
about it. I won't give a damn.
You're truly cruel.
Ayanokoji, Ryuen, all the
unwashed masses out there...
I'll crush anyone who comes after me.
This school's got such crazy rules...
and I'm loving it!